pegym.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy - PEGymPEGym

Written by: [Rob Michaels](https://www.pegym.com/author/rob-michaels)

## Our Privacy Policy in a Nutshell

Your privacy is important to you, and therefore it’s important to PEGym.com (“We”). At PE Gym.com our policy follows a few basic principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * At PEGym.com, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, PEGym.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. PEGym.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how PEGym.com’s visitors use its website.  PEGym.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. However, PEGym.com does not disclose such information and does not use such information to identify its visitors, unless to ban a user who breaks our Terms of Service.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to PEGym.com’s websites choose to interact with PEGym.com in ways that require PEGym.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that PEGym.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our forums to provide a username and email address. In each case, PEGym.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with PEGym.com. PEGym.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

PEGym.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, PEGym.com may monitor the most popular visited pages on the site or use spam screened by the forums to help identify spam.

## Protection of Personally-Identifying Information

PEGym.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees and contractors, PEGym.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law. If you are a registered user of PEGym.com and have supplied your email address, PEGym.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with PEGym.com and our services. We primarily use our website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. PEGym.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Like most websites, PEGym.com uses cookies to help PEGym.com identify and track visitors, their usage of PEGym.com website, and their website access preferences. PEGym.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using PEGym.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of PEGym.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Ads

Ads appearing on PEGym.com may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by PEGym.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, PEGym.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in PEGym.com’s sole discretion. PEGym.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
